联邦调查局警告
本片画面已经定为R级
20世纪福克斯家庭娱乐公司
光风暴娱乐公司
20世纪福克斯电影公司 出品
光风暴娱乐公司 摄制
詹姆斯・卡梅隆 作品
主演：阿诺德・施瓦辛格
主演：杰米莉・李・柯迪斯
真 实 的 谎 言
（瑞士，乔伯湖）
主演：汤姆・阿诺德
主演：比尔・帕克斯顿
主演：迪・卡雷利
主演：埃尔塔・马里克
主演：艾丽泽・达什库
主演：戈兰特・哈斯洛夫
查尔登・海斯顿 …… 斯宾瑟・特里尔比
选角导演：马里・芬
音乐：布拉德・费德尔
服装设计：玛琳・斯图尔特
视觉特效总监：约翰・布鲁诺
亲爱的，我到家了
Honey, I'm home.
知道
Roger that.
时间刚刚好
Copy at the boathouse. Right on time.
费絮，快进来，哈瑞已经进去了
Faisil, get your butt in here. Harry's inside.
好的，我来啦
Yeah, yeah, I'm coming. I'm coming.
老爹没教你要随手关门吗？
Hey, were you born in a barn?
我是孤儿
Whorehouse.
在你附近有4只狗
All right. You got your fur-coated razor blade there...
还有一堆带枪的人
and a bunch of guys with guns.
我现在换上无线耳机
I'm switching to sub-vocal now.
听到了吗？
Check, check.
“知心哥哥”广播电台开始播音
It' s talk radio. You're on the air.
好的，你边上的守卫已经走开了
That guard nearest to you is moving away.
电影剪辑：康拉德・布夫\n马克・戈德布拉特\n理查德・哈里斯
哈瑞来到餐厅后门，现在进去了
He's at the service door. He's inside.
这是什么？
再加点蒜
是喂狗的吗？
把这些丢掉！
快点！
您好？
很高兴见到你
你看到克莱了吗？
Have you seen Khaled yet?
看到了，就在那儿
Yep, there he is.
有钱佬为什么总是长不高？
How come billionaires are always short?
抱歉
Excuse me.
谢谢
Thank you.
上校！您好，真高兴再次见到你
Colonel! How are you? It's so good to see you again.
对，好久没见了
Yes, it's been a long time.
很好
Terrific.
那小子是谁？
Who was that guy?
请你帮我拿一下，谢谢
Could you hold this for a second? Thanks.
艺术指导：皮特・拉蒙特
你该穿过大厅，向楼梯走去
You should be crossing the main foyer, heading for the stairs.
摄影指导：罗素・卡本特
OK，继续向前走
Keep moving. Keep moving.
执行制片：罗伯特・史利弗　雷・桑切妮　劳伦斯・卡山诺夫
我在图书室
I'm in the library,
正朝二楼的阳台走去
heading out to the second-floor balcony.
编剧：詹姆斯・卡梅隆
编剧：克劳德・茨迪\n西蒙・迈克尔\n迪迪埃・卡民卡
制片：詹姆斯・卡梅隆\n史黛芬妮・奥斯汀
现在接上数据机，开始传送
Modem in place. Transmitting now.
接收到了
Affirmatory.
连接速度不错
It's a good hook-up.
档案防拷贝，我需要点时间解锁
These are encrypted files. It's going to take me a few minutes.
我找到密码了
I got your password.
厕所在哪里？
我急死了
在楼下左手边
导演：詹姆斯・卡梅隆
完美…你说是吗？
Magnificent, isn't it?
的确
Yes, quite.
克莱的朋友我都认识，但从没见过你
I thought I knew Khaled's friends, but I don't believe I've met you before.
是没见过，否则绝忘不了你
We haven't met, because I certainly would remember.
我叫伦奎斯特，哈瑞・伦奎斯特
Renquist, Harry Renquist.
我是琼娜・斯葛纳
Juno Skinner.
琼娜・斯葛纳
快点！
Come on!
“琼娜是古董艺术商”
"Juno Skinner, arts and antiquities dealer...
“专攻波斯古物鉴赏”
specializing in ancient Persia."
如果没看错，这该是古波斯艺术品
This is Persian, if I'm not mistaken.
很好，准确地说
Very good.
它是公元前6世纪的作品
Sixth century BC, to be exact.
你喜欢那段历史吗？
Do you like the period?
喜欢得紧
I adore it.
哈瑞，出问题了
We got a problem.
外面的守卫非常紧张
Guards are going ape shit down there.
我替克莱买进不少
Acquired most of these pieces for Jamal.
你跳探戈吗？
Do you tango?
探戈？
Tango?
哈瑞，你没时间跳探戈舞啦，伙计
Harty, you do not have time to tango, buddy.
你听到了吗？
You copy?
别像猫闻到腥一样赖着不走
Don't be stopping to smell the roses now.
好不好？
You hear me?
你得马上离开
You gotta get out of there.
耶！档案已经破解了
Yes! Files are unlocked!
伟大的费絮再次成功
Fast Faisil strikes again.
宝贝，我真是无往不胜
I'm in. I'm down, baby.
我已闻到她的体香，我要一亲芳泽…
I got my hand up her dress, and I am going for the gold...
快点拷贝文件，别没完没了的
Just copy the goddam files, okay?
哇！我本以为…
Wow. And I thought this was just gonna be...
这次又是些有钱人开的无聊聚会
another bunch of boring bankers and oil billionaires.
你现在是分秒必争，甩掉那婊子
Seconds count. Ditch the bitch.
曲终人散，我得向你告别
Unfortunately, I have to leave.
我得赶下一趟飞机
I have a plane to catch.
嗯，有空给我电话
Well, call me sometime.
我的办公室在罗马
My offices are in Rome.
我一定会的
I would like that.
天呀，才一会功夫
Son of a bitch is with her two minutes,
她就想跟他结婚生子
and she's ready to bear his children.
舞王，你打算怎么退朝啊？
Twinkle toes, what's your exit strategy?
当然是光明正大地从前门走出去
I'm going to walk right out of the front gate.
精神可嘉，但方法不可取
Ballsy. Stupid, but ballsy.
先生，我可以看一下你的请柬吗？
Sir, may I see your invitation, please?
看好了，这就是我的请柬
Sure. Here is my invitation.
糟了，我们快去接应
Shit. Here we go.
人算不如天算
Slight change in plans.
待着别动！
Stay!
我们正赶往下面的集合点
We're en route to the lower rendezvous point.
重复，在下面集合点支援你
Repeat, back-up rendezvous point!
小心！
Watch it!
傻蛋，冰上开车能不滑吗？
It's called ice, and it's slick.
哈瑞，你听到了吗？
Harry, do you copy? Whoa!
好了
I got it.
可恶！
Shit!
喔！
Whoops!
天啊！
Oh, my God!
哇！稳住！没事！
Whoa! I got it! I got it! I got it!
- 来了，来了！  - 要命！
- There he is! - Shit!
嗨，哥们
Hi, guys.
真不敢相信
That worked good.
你就这样大摇大摆走了出来
Right out the old front gate.
向后靠一下
Can you lean back a second?
走吧，我们还能赶上飞机
Let's go. We can still make our flight.
好了，这是哈瑞・伦奎斯特的
All right, that's it for Mr. Renquist.
我的呢？
Okay, go.
这是哈瑞・达斯克的皮夹…
We got Harry Tasker billfold,
护照、票根
Harry Tasker passport, ticket stub.
旅馆帐单
Hotel bill, Tasker.
还有两张日内瓦的明信片
I got two postcards here from Geneva.
这是你家里的钥匙
Got some house keys right there...
另外，这是瑞士雪村的纪念品
and I've got a souvenir Swiss snowing village.
- 干嘛？  - 送给达娜的，笨蛋
- What's that for? - It's for Dana, stupe.
给小孩买礼物，是做父亲的责任
Bring your kid home a gift, the dad thing.
真感人
Nice touch.
明天8点来接我
Pick me up tomorrow at 8:00.
好的
Will do.
他们10点听取报告
The debriefing is at 10:00.
- 8点见，拜拜  - 喂，哈瑞
- See you at 8:00. Bye. - Hey, Harry.
你是不是漏了样东西？
Did you forget something?
好兄弟！
What a team.
快去睡吧，好伙计
Sleep fast, buddy.
亲爱的，旅途愉快吗？
Hi, honey. How was your flight?
- 很好   - 那就好
- It was fine. - Good.
在瑞士买了这个雪村球送给你
Brought you a little gift from Switzerland. Snowy village.
谢谢你，爸，我从没有过这种玩具
Wow. Thanks, Dad. I've never had one of these.
一家人客气啥？
You're welcome.
快点，不然上学要迟到了
You're late for school. You better get going.
别忘了喂狗
Don't forget to feed Gizmo.
好的
Okay.
真差劲
It's pretty lame.
- 我要迟到了  - 我也是
- I'm late. - Yeah, me too.
展销会还好吧？
How'd it go at the convention?
是不是让别的推销员很嫉妒？
Make all the other salesmen jealous?
好得让你做梦都想不到
It was fantastic. You wouldn't believe it.
我真想让你看看我们是多么的风光
You should have been there. We were the big hit of the show.
我们展出了最新款680系列订货系统
With that new model ordering system, the 680 I told you about...
下单时，只要输入客户名字…
I can write up an order and immediately...
马上就能看到他的信用好不好
as soon as the customer's name comes up, you see what his credit line is...
过往记录，折扣…
what he has ordered in the past, what discount he has gotten.
所有细节都有
Every little detail.
听起来不错
Sounds great.
是很不错，我爱死这门事业了
It's fantastic. That's why I love the computer business.
水管工来电话了
Listen, the plumber called.
他说要挖个大洞什么的，要600美金
He says he has to dig under the slab or something that's gonna cost $600.
无所谓啦
That's okay.
有所谓！这是敲诈
It's not okay. It's extortion.
那你怎么对他说？
What did you tell him?
我和他上床，他减我100
I slept with him and he said he'd knock off $100.
辛苦你了，晚上见
That's good thinking. Bye, honey.
哈！
Hello!
达娜
Boy,
我第一次做炮弹飞人时
I remember the first time I got shot out of a cannon.
就是你这身打扮
早安，快去上学
Good morning. Go to school.
我是要走了
Yeah, I am.
谢啦，亲爱的
Thanks, dear.
试试这个
Check these out.
看看
Check them out.
影像从哪里来的？
Where's the image coming from?
那边的CCD香烟盒
Got a CCD camera
里面装有摄像头发射器
and a transmitter in a pack of smokes out there.
厉害吧？
It's pretty cool, huh?
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
爸，再见
Bye, Dad!
达娜
她在偷钱
She's ripping you off.
我就知道
I knew it.
快走！
Let's go!
太晚了，爸，我赶时间，拜拜
Can't stop! I'm late! Bye, Dad!
天杀的
God. Shit.
啥小孩，用10秒的喜悦换来30年痛苦
Kids. Ten seconds of joy, 30 years of misery.
我结过三次婚，从没蠢到想要小孩
I got married three times, but at least I was never dumb enough to have any.
我教过她，她不该偷钱的
She shouldn't be stealing. I taught her better than that.
她已经不当你和海伦是父母亲了
You're not her parents any more, you and Helen.
罗斯和麦当娜才是他们想要的
Her parents are Axl Rose and Madonna.
每天5分钟关爱
Five minutes a day you spend with her
怎比得上偶像巨星的威力
can't compete with that bombardment.
老爹，你太落伍啦
You're outgunned, Daddy-o.
这并不代表你不称职
It's not just because you're a bad parent.
现在的小孩…
Kids today...
比我们那会儿要早熟10年
are ten years ahead of where we were at the same age.
- 早  - 早安，达斯克先生
- Morning. - Morning, Mr. Tasker.
你一定认为她还是处女之身
I bet you think she's still a virgin.
别开玩笑了，她才…她今年几岁了？
Don't be ridiculous. She's only... What is she now?
14岁
She's 14.
她才14岁
She's only 14.
可她的荷尔蒙增长过快
Her hormones are going like an alarm.
说不定已跟哪个骑摩托的上过床了
It's even money she lets that physicist on the bike boink her.
- 达娜不会的  - “达娜不会的”
- Not Dana. - "Not Dana."
自欺欺人，你还当她是纯洁少女？
Denial. It's not just a river in Egypt no more, is it?
她偷钱…可能就是为了去堕胎
She's probably stealing the money to pay for an abortion.
你可以开门了
Why don't you open the door?
或是买毒品
Or drugs.
其实我常丢钱
Twenty here, 50 there.
还以为是我太太男朋友偷的
I figured my wife's boyfriend was taking it.
因为他什么都拿
He takes everything else.
连冰箱的啤酒都不放过
There's never a beer in the goddam fridge.
你不是搬出去了吗？
Thought you moved out.
又搬回来了啦
I had to move back in.
因为律师说…
My lawyer said
这样在分财产时对我有利
it'd give me a better shot at getting the house during the property settlement,
别换话题，你还欠我200块呢
but don't change the subject. You still owe me 200 bucks.
早安，珍妮斯
Good morning, Janice.
早安，先生们
Good morning.
请向扫描器确认身份
Identify yourselves to the scanner.
哈瑞・达斯克，10024号
Harry Tasker, 10024.
亚伯・吉普森，34991号
Albert Gibson, 34991.
（欧米茄部门，最后的防线）
好了，法兰斯
All right, Frances.
你可以离开了，谢谢
I don't believe we need you any longer now. Thank you.
怎么样，昨晚上“干”得爽不爽？
Sweet Jesus. You sure screwed the pooch last night, didn't you?
你让我怎么去面对你们的完败？
Would you please tell me how I can see this as anything but a total disaster?
“完败”这个字眼未免太过了吧？
"Total" is a strong word.
情况也并不是想象的那么糟
There are different degrees of totality.
总要一分为二
It's a scale, really,
一方面我们干得不错
with a perfect mission on one end...
而另一方面呢，我们是干得不爽…
and then a total pooch screw on the other, and we're more on this...
费絮，你是新加入哈瑞这伙的吧？
Faisil, you're new on Harry's team, aren't you?
是的
Yes.
你这菜鸟油腔滑调的
So what makes you think the slack...
不怕我革你职吗？
I cut him in any way translates to you?
我马上给你看我们获得的资料
Let me show you what we got.
我们怀疑克莱
Jamal Khaled. We think he's dirty,
就窃取了他的财务档案
so we raid his private financial files.
发现国际商业银行汇给他1亿美元
One hundred million in wire transfers from the Commerce Bank International.
肯定是某国付给他的恐怖活动经费
Which is a front for certain countries to finance terrorist activities.
也是我们认为会有大事发生的原因
That's why we think something really big is going down.
一周前，有4枚多重独立导向弹头…
We know that a week ago four MIRV warheads were smuggled...
从哈萨克斯坦共和国偷运出来
out of the former Soviet Republic of Kazakhstan.
我们断定是克莱买下了这批核武器
We think Khaled's group bought the nukes
并准备运进美国本土
and is trying to bring them to US soil.
说来说去都是我猜，我猜猜
So far this is not blowing my skirt up, gentlemen.
你们就没点实在点的东西吗？
Don't you have anything remotely substantial?
哈瑞，有没有确切点的？
Harry, do you have any hard data?
没什么可让你提神的
Nothing you would call rock-hard.
伤脑筋的事倒有一大把
Actually it's pretty limp, sir.
那你们最好在
Then perhaps you better get some...
他们找上门来，搞跨白宫前…
before somebody parks an automobile in front of the White House...
把他们干掉！
with a nuclear weapon in the trunk.
就是这么的平庸
It's not like he's saving the world or anything.
一个人前低三下四的推销员
He's a sales rep, for Christ's sake.
每回我睡不着
Whenever I can't sleep,
就要他说说一天的工作
I ask him to tell me about his day.
6秒钟不到，我就睡着了
Six seconds and I'm out.
他倒是自视甚高，自以为了不起
He acts like he's curing cancer or something.
听你口气，周末你们又没出去玩
I guess this means you didn't get away for the weekend after all.
哈瑞要出差
Harry had to go out of town.
难怪
I'm shocked.
唉，你知道哈瑞的
Yeah, well, you know Harry.
怎么啦？
What's up?
你看
Check this out.
克莱居然给了琼娜200百万
There's a $2 million disbursement from Khaled to Juno Skinner.
就是派对中的那个美女
That's right. The babe at the party.
这有什么？她一直在替克莱买古董
That doesn't mean anything. She buys antiquities for Khaled.
他把买古董的帐记在另一本帐簿里
He keeps his antique buys on a completely separate ledger.
根据最新市场买春行情
This is a little above market rate for the horizontal bop...
从来没人出过这么高的价钱
even for a total biscuit like her.
好吧，我需要她所有的资料
I want a complete work up on her.
知道她在哪儿吗？
Do we know where she is?
就在这座城市　　　开玩笑吧？
Right here in River City.
她虽住罗马，但也替史密森做事
She lives in Rome, but she does stuff for the Smithsonian.
有许多外交联络
She has a lot of diplomatic connections,
在这也设了办公室
so she has offices here.
看来是时候让专家出马了
I guess it's time to send in a specialist.
跳个探戈吧？
Care to tango?
我的荣幸
Yes, I would.
两个贱货
Assholes.
一切就绪，传真机、小灵通
It's all set up. You got a fax machine, ghost phones,
都是你称心的
all the usual stuff.
你以伦奎斯特的名义…
You have a suite at the Marquis Hotel
住在马盖兹旅馆
under the name of Renquist.
我们再演习一遍
Reality check. Let's go.
我叫哈瑞・伦奎斯特
My name is Harry Renquist.
在旧金山开设艺术咨询公司
I own an art consulting firm in San Francisco.
我和斯葛纳小姐有预约
I have an appointment with Miss Skinner.
- 哈瑞  - 哈
- Harry! - Hello.
哈
Hello.
我知道会再见到你
I thought I'd see you again.
但没料到会这么快
I just didn't know it would be so soon.
明明知道…我迫不及待
What's the point of waiting?
我同意
I agree.
听说你的客户在找…
Your clients are looking for something
能装饰大厅的艺术品？
for the lobby of their new headquarters?
给客人别开生面的印象
They would like to see something very dramatic.
让人刮目相看
那件很不错
That's a nice piece.
我和好几个人谈过
I talked to a number of people,
他们都大力推崇你
and they all said you're the one to see.
真的？你在研究我？
Really? Checking on me.
他们到底怎么说我呢？
So what did these people say about me exactly?
说你能看得懂古梵文，而且很精通
That you can read ancient Sanskrit without having to sound out the words...
但有些商贾和考古学家…
and other art dealers and archaeologists
却并不太喜欢你
don't like you very much.
那些家伙
Those wimps.
那是因为我能运用外交手段…
It's because I use my diplomatic contacts
购买一些珍贵古玩
to export cultural treasures...
而他们只能干瞪眼
from countries which tell them to take a hike.
看，都是些古波斯艺术品
Most of our pieces come from ancient Persia.
可惜都被埋葬在20尺深的地下…
Unfortunately, ancient Persia is 20 feet under the sand of...
伊朗、伊拉克和叙利亚挖到了宝
Iran, Iraq and Syria.
自然财大气粗，目空一切
Not the most popular places lately.
跟他们打交道
So I've had to become an expert...
黑白两道都要吃得开才行
in international diplomacy.
嗯，伦奎斯特先生
Well, Mr. Renquist?
有没有喜欢的？
Do you see anything you like?
也许吧
Maybe.
拜托，他们才不会…
Give me a break. I don't think...
在我的三明治里放窃听器
they bugged my tuna sandwich.
她向中东许多国家进口货物
She's importing stuff from all over the Mideast.
很可能也做洗钱、走私枪械的买卖
She could be moving money, guns, anything.
你一离开，小灵通就响个不停
The second you left, we started getting calls to the ghost numbers.
都在查询伦奎斯特
They were checking out the Renquist front.
继续监视他们，多派两个人过去
Let's step up the surveillance and put on two more guys.
马瑞，我说的是星期六
Maurizio, I said Saturday,
不是星期二
not Tuesday. Saturday.
斯葛纳小姐，我能和你说句话吗？
Miss Skinner, may I have a word with you, please?
蠢货，有头没脑的婊子
Stupid, undisciplined bitch.
看在钱的份上，我让你
It's a good thing you're paying me a lot of money.
你知不知道我们已经给人盯上了？
Do you realize there are surveillance teams watching this place right now?
你的电话也早已被人窃听了
Your telephones are almost certainly tapped.
而你却浑然不知，像个妓女…
And you were busy laughing and flirting
还忙着和伦奎斯特打情骂俏
like a whore with this Renquist...
我们查过他…
He checked out okay...
不怕一万，就怕万一
We do not tolerate mistakes.
那你想我怎么样？
What would you like me to do?
找出伦奎斯特的住处
Find out where this Renquist is.
这是泰可公司达斯克先生办公室
Hello, Tektel Systems. Mr. Tasker's office.
萧玲吗？我是海伦，我先生在吗？
Hi, Charlene? Hi, it's Helen. Is he in?
他在开会，达斯克夫人
Harry's in a sales meeting, Mrs. Tasker.
我试试，请稍等
Let me try him in there. Hold, please.
转给10024号
Relay, 10024.
“打电话者的身份是1168”
是找泰可公司的电话
It's a patch from Tektel.
海伦打来的
It's Helen.
甜心，你好，有什么事？
Hello, honey. How are you? What's going on?
对不起，打扰你开会了
Hi. I'm sorry to bother you in the middle of a meeting.
我和达娜想知道
It's just that Dana and I want to make sure
你会不会8点准时到家
you were gonna be home by 8:00.
为准备你的生日
We're going to a lot of trouble for your big birthday.
我们花了不少心思
We just wanted to make sure
所以要确定你一定会回家
that you were gonna be home.
没问题，一定会准时到家
Absolutely. This time you can count on me.
- 保证？  - 我保证
- Promise? - Trust me.
- 很好  - 就这样了
- Great. - Got to go. Bye.
再见
Bye.
达娜，你有病啊？
That's disgusting, Dana.
别激动嘛
Calm down.
有人在跟踪，在内线道的第三辆车
We got a friend. Three cars back on the inside lane.
自从离开旅馆后就一直跟踪
They've been on us since we left the hotel.
是那辆旅行车吗？　　　对
- You mean the station wagon? - Yes.
要我甩掉他们吗？
You want me to lose them?
不要，我们需要这条线索
No. We need this lead.
第七组在吗？
Unit Seven?
第七组在这里
Seven here.
你们3分钟后到乔治城购物中心
We need you at the Georgetown Mall in three minutes.
听到了，马上出发
Copy. We're rolling.
海伦会气死
Helen's gonna be pissed.
最烦恐怖份子这点
This is the problem with terrorists.
他们一点也不替别人着想
They're really inconsiderate when it comes to people's schedules.
太靠近了，离远点
好，在这里停车
Pull over here. This is good.
试音，一、二、三
Okay, testing, one, two, three.
我听到了
I got you. I got you. I got you.
他们一直跟着我们，车里有3个人
They're right with us. I make three of them in the car.
白痴
Dick head.
猪头
Blow me.
有两个人下车去跟踪你
I got a couple of them getting out of the car and coming after you.
你当我瞎的？
Think I'm blind?
你是有点像雷・查尔斯
You do look like Ray Charles.
有什么计划？
So what's the plan?
先跟他们来个亲密接触
Just trying to get a closer look at Beavis and Butt-head.
第三个人还在车里
There's a third one still in the car.
你看着他
Stay on him.
海伦，我是吉普…没什么
Hi, Helen. Yeah, it's Gib. Oh, not much.
是这样的
Listen,
哈瑞又回公司去拿东西了
Harry forgot something back at the office.
你也知道哈瑞记性不好
You know Harry.
是的，吉普，我很清楚他，再见
Yeah, Gib, I know Harry. Bye.
一会见
Bye. See you soon.
我就猜到
See?
哈瑞，第三个家伙不见了
I lost the third guy.
天啊
Shit!
要命
停一下！该死
Hold it! Shit!
冲个凉吧
Here. Cool off.
抱歉，吓到你了
Sorry about this.
小心，让路
Look out! Get out of the way!
嘿，别动
Hey! Freeze!
真是老天保佑
Oh, thank God.
开车
Get in the car.
看我的啦
Here we go.
我是联邦警官，正在追疑犯
Federal officer in pursuit of suspect.
对不起
Sorry.
哈瑞，你在哪里？
Harry, what's your 20?
公园的西面
Westbound in the park.
疑犯骑摩托车
Suspect is on a motorcycle,
马上会到法兰克林街
and he's coming out on Franklin.
知道了
Copy!
为预防他朝南转，我要你到14街去
I want you on 14th in case he turns south.
还有第七组到北边，好包围他
I want Seven on the north side to box him in.
要快，因为我马快不行了
Make it quick, because my horse is getting tired.
你的马？
Your horse?
他在那里
There he is! That's him!
快！
Come on!
绕到后面去
Go around to the back.
知道了
Copy that.
别挡着我
Out of my way!
走开
抱歉
Sorry.
借光
Excuse me.
- 我的天！  - 对不起
- Jesus! - Sorry.
开门
Open it!
抱歉，借过一下
Excuse me. Excuse me.
走开
Out of the way!
让开！快让路！
Move! Move! Move!
我们是联邦警官
Federal officer!
马上下车弃械投降
Get down! Now! Get off or die!
- 马上下车！  - 让开
- Get down! Now! - Move!
转过去，不准动！
Turn around! Hold still!
快点
Come on!
哇！
Whoa!
不准动！
Hold still!
请你替我按顶楼，好吗？
Will you press the button for the top floor, please?
谢谢你
Thank you.
救命！
Help!
闭嘴！
Shut up!
你说句话呀！
Say something.
好个大种马
That's a fine animal.
靠着窗玻璃
Stay against the glass!
准备出发了
Come on.
实在对不起
So sorry.
待在这儿，不准动！
Stay there! Don't move!
走，快走！
Come on, come on, come on!
好，向后退
Okay, back up.
退后
Back up.
你行的，加点劲
You can do it. Come on.
马儿，你真乖
Good horse. Good.
对，对，向后退
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, go back now.
加油，发挥团队精神
Come on. Yeah, that's teamwork now.
继续拉，别停
Keep pulling. Come on.
再多拉点儿
A little bit more.
马儿乖
That a boy.
好了
Okay.
你脑子里都在想什么啊？
What the hell were you thinking?
都是你坏的事，让他逃跑了
I had the guy, and you let him get away.
我讲话时要看着我
Look at me when I talk to you.
你算什么警察嘛？
What kind of a cop are you anyway?
嗨，亲爱的
Hi, honey.
我知道你很不高兴，对不起
I know you're upset. I'm sorry.
不过，我尽快赶回来了
I hurried home as fast as I could.
没关系
It's okay.
真对不起
I'm sorry.
谢谢你给我过生日
Thank you for the party.
派对是很不错
Yeah, it was great.
嘿
Hey.
就是他
That's him.
在那儿暂停
Pause it right there.
他叫萨里姆・阿布・阿兹
Salim Abu Aziz.
这家伙是真正的狂热份子
This guy is really hard-core. Highly fanatical.
他脑筋有问题
The man's a real psycho.
和许多汽车爆炸案有关
He's been linked to dozens of car bombings.
去年罗马咖啡厅的爆炸案
You know that cafe bomb in Rome last year?
就是他的杰作
That was his.
还有里斯本的727案件
As well as a 727 out of Lisbon.
他是恐怖份子
This guy's a major player.
他甚至组织自己的党派
Now he's formed his own splinter faction
称为红伐党
called Crimson Jihad.
他认为别的恐怖组织太温和
I guess he thought the other terrorists were too warm and fuzzy for him.
他们称他为沙蜘蛛
They call him the Sand Spider.
为什么？
Why?
可能是因为听起来很恐怖吧
Probably because it sounds scary.
各位，很不错
This is impressive, gentlemen.
但如果能知道他在哪就更好了
It would be even more impressive if you actually knew where he was.
我们会找到他的
We'll get him.
拜托在这停一下
Why don't you pull over here?
为什么？
What's up?
昨晚我让海伦很失望
I really screwed up with Helen last night.
所以想请她去个吃午餐
I'm going to see if she's available for lunch
好好安抚一下
to smooth things over.
要我等你吗？
You just want me to hang?
好
Just hang.
那我就等你
I'll just be hanging.
请等一下
Hold, please.
二线是你的神秘情人
It's your mystery man on two.
是西蒙吗？
Simon?
喔，我的天
Oh, my God.
喂，是西蒙吗？
Hello? Simon?
西蒙？
Simon?
是，没有别人
Yes, I can talk.
你是说现在？
You mean right now?
好，我们可以见面
Yes, I can meet you.
我等不及了
Okay, I can't wait.
再见
Bye.
你能不能代我1个钟头？
Can you cover me for an hour?
1个钟头就能完事？太快了吧？
Just an hour? You should tell that stud to take more time.
别那么大声，当初真不该告诉你
Would you shut up? I should have never told you about him.
好好享受
Have a good time.
别忘了我呀
Get a little bit for me while you're at it.
喂，停一下！
Hey! Hold it!
混蛋！
Fucker!
怎么搞的？病了吗？
What's going on? Sick?
怎么像见了鬼似的
Looks like you got gut-kicked.
是海…海伦
It's Hel... It's Helen... It's Helen.
我猜和海伦有关
It has something to do with Helen, I'm guessing.
海伦…
Helen...
海伦她…
Helen is...
她有婚外恋
is having an affair.
老兄，欢迎加入绿帽俱乐部
Welcome to the club, man.
怎么会是海伦？
It can't be. Not Helen.
刚开始都认为不可能，伙计
Nobody thinks it could happen to them the first time.
我第二任太太也是这样，记得吗？
Same thing happened to me with wife number two, remember?
当初毫无迹象
I had no idea nothing was going on.
一回家东西全搬空了
I come home, and the house is empty.
她居然把制冰盒也拿走了
She even took the ice cube trays out of the freezer.
你说，这婊子要制冰盒干嘛呢？
What kind of a sick bitch takes the ice cube trays out of the freezer?
海伦不会的
It's not Helen.
嘿，哈瑞，听着，海伦仍然爱你
Helen still loves you.
她只想找点刺激，没什么大不了的
She just wants to bang this guy for a while. It's nothing serious.
你很快就会习惯
You'll get used to it soon
别再安慰我
Stop cheering me up!
那你认为该怎么样呢？
What'd you expect?
她是活生生的女人
Helen's a flesh-and-blood woman,
而你成天不在家
and you're never there.
这是迟早的事
It was just a matter of time.
我建议你，伙计，还是以事业为重
I say we concentrate on work.
每次我受到打击，就这么做
That's what I do every time my life turns to dog shit.
致力于工作，伤口就会慢慢抚平
I concentrate on work, and that gets me by.
放心，伙计，你会很忙的
Right, buddy? It's gonna be great.
知道吗，多抓恐怖份子
We're gonna catch some terrorists.
然后修理他们
We're gonna beat the crap out of them.
你会觉得很有成就感呢
You're going to feel a hell of a lot better.
小心头，你别愁了
Watch your head. Okay. All right.
女人，相处不能，宰杀不得
Women. Can't live with 'em, can't kill 'em.
我今天到你办公室去了
I came by your office today.
因为我在附近办事
I was in the area,
想邀你出去吃饭
and I thought you might want to have lunch.
真的？那你一定刚好与我错过了
Really? Well, you must have just missed me.
没错，你同事说你有事出去了
That's what they said. They said you had to run out or something.
因为有份急件…
It was this rush job
地方法院等着要
They needed these documents down at the district courthouse.
可是我们的打印机坏了
So, of course, the big problem... our printer shut down.
我只好到三楼去印，可惜机种不同
So I went to the third floor to use theirs,
磁片格式不兼容
but they have the 1720.
1720打印机印不了
Of course, the disk isn't formatted for the 1720.
只好又回到楼上重新格式化
So I had to go back upstairs and reformat...
再回到楼下去用他们的打印机
go back downstairs and use their printer.
好不容易弄好了，车又不能发动
By the time I got there, I couldn't get my car to start.
然后交通又…我几乎没赶到
Then traffic... I barely got there.
这就是你的小插曲
So a little excitement in an otherwise dull day.
结果如何？
Did it work out okay?
喔，很好
Yeah. Great.
我去拿甜点
I'll check on dessert.
我吃完了
I'm done.
好处是…他让我们全权处理
The great thing is that he's practically given us a blank cheque on wiretaps.
我现在正监听琼娜的手下和客户
I set them up on all of Juno's shipping agents and her clients.
费絮把红伐党在美国…
Faisil's made a list of all the possible contacts...
可能接触的列了表
the Crimson Jihad may have in this country.
所以我们只要坐着…
Now all we have to do is sit around...
难道这种国家安全大事…
Hey. This national security stuff boring you?
还会让你无聊吗？
我要监听她的电话
Put a tap on her phone.
已经在监听了
What? I already did that.
我是指海伦
I'm talking about Helen's.
我要监听她公司和家里电话
Put a tap on her office line and the house. Now.
好主意，你过来一下
Come over here for a second. That sounds great.
让我来告诉你吧，两个字：
I want to ask you about something. I got two words to describe that idea...
“疯狂”
In-sane.
你知道未经许可监听犯法
An unauthorized wiretap's a felony. You know that.
你天天都在做，少跟我说教
And you're doing it 20 times a day, so don't give me that crap.
快去
Do it.
（男性压低声音）
喂
Hello?
海伦，我是西蒙，讲话安全吗？
Helen, it's Simon. Is it safe to talk?
可以
Yes, go ahead.
不能讲太久，我要见你
I can't talk long.
明天一起吃午餐好吗？
Can you meet me for lunch tomorrow? I must see you.
我想可以，在哪里？
I suppose so. Where?
1点钟，老地方
Same place, 1:00.
我得走了，明天见
I have to go now. See you tomorrow.
记住，我需要你
Remember, I need you.
明天一起吃午饭好吗？
I thought that we might have lunch together tomorrow.
哎呀…真不巧
You know... darn it...
我和艾丽约好去逛街
I'm going to meet Allison. We're going to go shopping. Sorry.
没关系
No problem.
其实我认为你全搞错了
I think you're going about this whole thing all wrong.
女人需要听些甜言蜜语
Women... they like you to talk to them.
也许你该表现出温柔的那一面
Maybe it's just that you're not in touch with your feminine side.
因为我看“莎莉探讨时间”…
I was watching Sally Jessy Raphael...
算我多嘴
All right.
所有装备都在这，有遥感传送器
I got all the usual stuff here... a telemetry burst transmitter.
全球定位追踪器、监听器和供电器
I got a GPS tracker, an audio transmitter and a power supply.
全缝在皮包衬里下面，还有，哈瑞？
I've got it sewn into the lining here... Hey, Harry?
她来啦，小心
If you need to talk, speak into the purse.
她会开到我们前面去
Here she comes. She's gonna pop out right in front of us. Watch this.
宾果　　　对啊
Bingo.
她好像要去中国城
Looks like she's going into Chinatown.
她在停车
She's parking.
好了，现在用监听器
Okay, give me audio.
你确定没被跟踪？
You sure you weren't followed?
我照你教的不断往后看
No. I kept looking behind me like you taught me,
没见到有人跟踪
but I didn't see anyone.
很好，现在情况有点紧张
Okay, it's just that things are a bit hot right now.
一有状况，我就得马上离开
If I get a signal, I may have to leave suddenly.
我了解
I understand.
冒险是我的工作
Look, it's my job to take risks,
但你却不需要一起冒险
but not yours.
我不该拖你下水
I feel bad about bringing you into this,
但你是唯一能信任的人
but you're the only one I can trust.
你在执行任务吗？
Were you out on a mission?
这是秘密任务
We say "op," covert operation.
不过…比以前的要困难得多
And this one, well, got a little rough.
比开罗的任务还困难？
Worse than Cairo?
开罗
Cairo.
比起来，开罗任务就像吃饭一样
Cairo was a day at the beach next to this.
这家伙可能是间谍
The guy's a spook.
替谁工作呢？
But for whom?
可能借着她来找到你
He could be working her to get to you.
- 你有没有看昨天的报纸  - 看了
- Did you read the papers yesterday? - Yes.
有时候它所报导的
Sometimes a story is a mask...
就是我的秘密任务
for a covert operation.
你有没有看到万豪酒店…
You see two men killed...
厕所内有两人被杀
in a restroom and two unidentified men...
还有两个身份不明的人…
in a running shootout,
在酒店内追逐的新闻？
ending at the Marriott?
那是你干的？
That was you?
不错，你真厉害
- Me. - You're very good.
居然看出我的手法来
You recognized my style.
你有这方面的天才
You're a natural at this.
这家伙是冒牌货
The guy's a fake.
居然冒充我们的案子
He's taking credit for our moves.
- 后来呢？  - 没什么好提的
- What happened? - Hardly worth talking about.
那两个已经挂了
Two of them won't bother me again.
真难以置信
Unbelievable.
你在追另一个吗？
You chase done?
不错，不管多危险
Something came over me.
我一定要抓住他
I had to nail this guy no matter what the risk.
当时真惊险，有好几次被他…
Pretty hairy. I thought he had me a couple of times, but I...
其实我不该居功自傲的
I really can't take credit.
为什么？
Why not?
那全是训练的功劳
It's the training.
使我们变得很犀利
It shapes you into a lethal instrument.
这些都是反射动作，不需思考
You react in a microsecond without thinking.
我挺喜欢这家伙
I'm starting to like this guy.
当然仍要杀掉他，那是不可饶恕的
We still gotta kill him. That's a given, you know.
（旧车行）
这家伙居然是他妈的旧车推销员
The guy is a goddamned used car salesman.
事情越来越精彩
This keeps getting better and better!
对不起，我知道你很痛苦
I'm sorry. I know this has gotta be painful.
但是，确实很有趣
But you gotta admit it's funny.
如果换成别人，你也会笑破肚皮的
If it was just some idiot, not you...\nyou'd be laughing your ass off.
大鱼又要上钩了
One born every minute.
它也要你，你感觉到了吗？
It wants you too. Feel it vibrate?
- 要不要试试车？  - 好呀
- Say, how about a little spin? - Sure.
其实车代表你的形象
See, it's not just a car. It's a total image. An identity.
因此要有所选择
You have to go for it.
这并不是什么高科技的跑车
This isn't some high-tech sports car.
说真话，性能也不怎么样
To tell you the truth, it doesn't even handle that great.
但那不是重点，对不对？
But that's not the idea, is it?
重要的是钓女人，是不是？
What are we talking about here? Pussy, right?
没错
Absolutely.
大家都知道，这种车是女人的最爱
Let's face it. The 'Vette gets 'em wet.
但光靠车还不够
But it's not enough.
如果要成功，还得再加上点花招
If you really want to close escrow, you gotta have an angle.
那你一定有花招？
I suppose you have an angle.
百战百胜的绝招
It's killer.
我们都看得出来
I mean, look at me. I'm not that much to look at.
我并不是什么帅哥
No, no, no. I can be honest.
却有一堆女人排着队等我
But I got 'em lining up,
而且都很漂亮
and not just the skanks either.
当然也有丑的
Well, some are.
你用什么绝招呢？
What's your angle?
抱歉，这是秘密
No, sorry. Trade secret.
你仔细想想看
Okay, just ask yourself:
女人最想要什么？
What do women really want?
例如结婚多年的家庭主妇
You take these bored housewives married to the same guy for years.
生活淡得像白开水一样
They're stuck in a rut.
她们需要解放
They need some release.
希望过冒险和刺激的生活
The promise of adventure, a hint of danger.
我就替她们完成心愿
I create that for them.
所以基本上你是个大骗子
So basically you're lying your ass off the whole time.
我没办法做到
I couldn't do that.
拜托，又不是童子军
What are you, a Boy Scout?
就当在演戏一样，真的很棒
Think of it as playing a role. It's fantasy.
利用她们的梦想…
You gotta work on their dreams...
让她们每天有几个钟头的快乐时光
get them out of their daily suburban grind for a few hours.
那她们的先生怎么办呢？
What about their husbands?
管他的
Dickless!
老实说，如果他们不冷落太太…
I mean, let's face it. If they took care of business...
怎么会轮到我，你懂吧？
I'd be out of business, you know what I mean?
那些白痴们
Those idiots.
拜托别开得这么快
You mind keeping it under 90?
我牙医的钱还没付清呢
I'm still trying to pay for this dental work.
那么你现在的对象是谁？
So, who are you working on right now?
我随时都有好几个在手上
I always got a couple on the hook.
但其中一个，已经在我掌握之中
There's this one right now, I got her panting like a dog.
真棒
It's great.
她是做什么的？
What does she do?
好像是秘书之类
Some sort of legal secretary or something.
就是那种又紧张、又保守的女人
You know, uptight and conservative.
但如果点燃的话，她会比火还热
But she could be so hot if she wanted to be.
所以和你在一起，她就会燃烧起来
And with you, she gets to be real hot.
火辣辣的！真会被她溶化掉
Red hot! Her thighs steam.
她们就像垂死的植物
It's like a dying plant.
只要一点水就会复苏
Just needs a little water.
真可怜，嫁给个没情调的笨蛋
Married to some boring jerk.
没情调的笨蛋？
Some boring jerk?
他不知道该好好珍惜她
He doesn't appreciate her.
其实只要能点燃她
She's like all these babes.
就可以随心所欲了
You get their pilot lit, they can suck-start a leaf-blower.
她的身材真是一流，尤其是那双峰
She's got the most incredible body, and a pair of titties...
看得你直流口水
make you want to stand up and beg for buttermilk.
臀部又紧又翘
Ass like a ten-year-old boy.
那么床上功夫一定一流啦
So, then she must be really good in bed then, huh?
慢点，会来不及转弯
Slow down. You'll miss the turn.
你看…
See?
车子和你是绝配，狂野型的
You and this car were made for each other. Why fight it?
我有好几个客户喜欢这部车
Sure, I got a couple other buyers on the line,
但你最适合
but I like your style.
你认为怎么样？
So, what do you say?
要不要买下来呀？
Should we start up the paperwork?
让我考虑一下
Let me think about it.
给我一天时间，好吗？
Hold it for me for a day, okay?
嘿，这可是看在你的份上
Hey, because it's you.
这是今天的记录
I got today's transcripts.
没什么事发生
Not much going on.
- 西蒙那边也没有？  - 没有
- Nothing from Simon? - No.
- 要我开吗？  - 把那一页给我
- My turn to drive? - Give me the page.
- 哪一页？  - 为何从9就跳到11
- What? - This jumped from page 9 to 11.
- 第10页呢？  - 一定是打错了
- Where's page 10? - It's gotta be a typo.
把第10页给我
Give me the goddam page!
好吧
你需要看心理医生
Seek help, Harry.
喂
Hello?
海伦，我需要你的帮助
Helen, I need your help.
今晚能见面吗？
Can you meet me tonight?
- 发生了什么事？  - 很严重
- What's happened? - It's serious.
8点钟在K街的…
Meet me on K Street...
K桥下见面
under the Key Bridge, 8:00 sharp.
上钩了
Gotcha.
糟糕，快8点了
Shit. It's almost 8:00.
她仍在家里
She's still at the house.
是皮包仍在家里
The purse is still at the house.
该死
Shit.
第二组、第七组，注意听
Unit Two, Unit Seven, immediate roll.
目标物在K街的K桥下
Acquire subject at K Street and Key Bridge.
开着红白相间的敞蓬车
Vehicle is red and white convertible.
你们只有6分钟
You got exactly six minutes.
等等，你疯了吗？
Wait a minute. Are you out of your mind?
你不能让别的案子调查员…
You can't pull agents off a priority surveillance...
来跟踪你太太
to follow your wife.
那是滥用职权，并且违反国家安全
That's a misappropriation of resources and a breach of national security.
你听到了吗？你会惹上大麻烦
You copy? You're losing it big-time, man.
我必须制止你
I have to stop you.
你想去告密？
What are you gonna do, tell?
这有关我们俩的前途
Look, goddam it. Both of our butts are on the line.
我知道你太太和人约会，你很不爽
So your life's in the crapper. Your wife's banging a used car salesman.
觉得丢脸，我知道
It's humiliating, I know,
但你要像个男子汉面对事实
but take it like a man!
你告我，我就告你
You tell on me, I tell on you.
你是什么意思？我毫无瑕疵
What are you talking about?\nI'm as clean as a preacher's sheets.
我干净得像…
I'm as clean as...
那次你为满足性欲…
What about when you blew a six-week operation...
把任务搞砸，怎么说？
because you were busy getting a blow-job?
你知道那件事？
You knew about that?
走法兰克林街，比较快
Let's take Franklin. It's quicker.
快，上车，快点，我们走
Quick, get in. Hurry up. Let's go.
这是第二组，看到疑犯的车子
Two here. Suspect vehicle in sight.
一男、一女
One male, one female.
别紧张
Now, don't be alarmed.
你不能被他们看到
If I'm spotted, it'd be best if they didn't see you.
所以在出城之前，最好把头放低
You should keep your head down till we're out of the city.
让我帮你
Here, let me help you.
就是这样
That's better.
女人将她的头放在男人的腿上
Now the woman has her head in the guy's lap.
他们向K桥南方进行
South bound on the Key Bridge.
第二组继续跟踪
Two in pursuit.
明白，第一组呼叫兀鹰号
Roger, Two. One to Condor,
看到疑犯吗？
you got a visual?
这是兀鹰号，看到了
Roger, One. This is Condor. Subject is in sight.
重复，已看到目标物
Repeat. We have the ball.
用红外线看得很清楚
We got a pretty good lockup on infrared.
她是把头放在男人的腿上
She's got her head in the guy's lap, all right.
她可能想睡觉
Maybe she's sleepy.
这是间安全的房子
This is a safe house.
在市区的房子太危险
My place in the city is a little too hot right now.
纽约的豪华套房也一样
So is the penthouse in New York.
你到底要我帮什么？
What is it exactly you need me to do?
海伦，我要你做我太太
I want you to be my wife.
可是我已经结婚了
But I'm married!
这是为巴黎的任务做掩护
It's just for the operation in Paris.
我需要个太太
I need to be married.
因为他们在找单身旅行的人
They'll be looking for a man travelling alone.
你要我去巴黎？
You want me to go to Paris?
对，先停伦敦再到巴黎
Paris, with a quick stopover in London.
海伦
组织中有个双重间谍，但不知是谁
There's a double agent in my outfit. I don't know who.
（美国航空公司 - 巴黎）
除了你，我不相信任何人
There's no one I can trust, except you.
你能离开几天吗？
Can you get away, just for a couple of days?
我不知道
I just don't know.
对不起，我不该催你
Of course. I'm rushing you. Forgive me.
坐下来，别拘束
Sit down. Make your self comfortable.
我再倒点酒给你
Let me pour you some more wine.
好的
I'll do it.
我愿意帮你
你真是救命恩人
You just saved my life.
而且非常勇敢
You are incredibly brave.
我必须提醒自己，你会有多么害怕
I have to remind myself of the fear you must be feeling.
只因为我没有害怕的权利
You see, for me fear is not an option.
为了增加真实性…
Now, in order to pull this cover story off...
我们必须看起来非常亲密
we have to look like two people who are completely intimate with each other.
否则会被敌人看穿
The enemy can spot a fake easily.
- 这就是我说的问题  - 对不起
- You see what I mean? - Sorry.
这种反应会使我们丧命的
That reaction could get us both killed.
- 对不起  - 这种事不能发生
- I'm sorry. - We can't afford that.
当然不行
试着放松自己
Try to relax.
因为除了哈瑞…
It's just been a long time...
已经很久没有别人那样碰我了
since anybody but Harry's touched me like that.
所以有点困难
It's a little difficult.
我知道，其实我也很笨拙
I know. It's awkward for me too.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
- 没关系，向后靠一点  - 我很好
- That's all right. Just sit back. - I'm okay.
这样好多了
There. That's better.
让自己慢慢溶入角色里
Just let yourself slip into the role.
就是这样
That's it.
现在很好
There you go.
放松自己
Just let yourself go.
很好
That's good.
非常不错
That's great.
就是这样
That's it.
不，我没办法
No, I can't do this. I can't do this.
- 怎么回事？  - 我做不来
- What's wrong? It's okay. - I cannot do this.
真的没办法
I cannot do this!
就算不是为我
If not for me...
你也要为国家
do it for your country?
天哪，别伤害我
Oh, God! Don't hurt me!
我会很听话的
I'll do whatever you want!
我什么也没做
Please! I didn't do anything!
该死
Damn it!
带她走！天哪，别伤害我
Take her! Take her! Oh, God, don't hurt me!
真他妈的要命
Son of a bitch!
坐下来
Sit down.
我叫你坐下来
I said sit down.
你替谁工作？
Who do you work for?
史坦、克斯勒、哥斯坦还有克普尼
Stern, Kessler, Goldstein & Krumpnick.
我只是个秘书
I'm just a legal secretary.
是吗？达斯克太太
Sure, Mrs. Tasker.
那你是替国际恐怖份子…
What were you doing with the international terrorist...
卡洛斯做速记吗？
Carlos the Jackal, taking dictation?
你加入他的党有多久？
How long have you been a member of his faction?
我根本不知道什么党
I don't know anything about a faction.
我在两个礼拜前…
I just met Simon...
遇到自称西蒙的他
or whoever you say he is...
就是你们所说的那个人
just a couple weeks ago.
我对他一点也不清楚
I barely know him.
但当我们抵达时，你们似乎很亲密
That's not what it looked like when we found you.
你怎么认识他的？
How did you meet him?
那是…
Well...
请帮我看着公事包，我带着它太危险
Keep this for me. I can't afford to be taken with it.
- 什么？  - 这关系着国家安全
- What? - It's a matter of national security.
求求你答应我，我会和你联络
Please, it's important. I'll contact you.
糟糕
Oh, shit.
（护照）
你为什么要继续见他？
Why did you continue to see him?
他说需要我帮忙
He said he needed my help.
不是因为他吸引了你？
Not because you were attracted to him?
不是
你一点也不喜欢他？
You were not attracted to him at all?
也许有一点
Well, maybe just a little.
你常做欺骗的事吗？
So, is cheating a common thing for you?
从来没有
Never.
所以这是第一次？
So you're telling me this was your first time?
我并没有欺骗
I wasn't cheating!
告诉我你先生的事
Tell me about your husband, Mrs. Tasker.
你是指哈瑞？
我该怎么说他呢？
What can I say about Harry?
他是电脑公司的推销员
He's a sales rep for a computer company.
所以和他做爱，再也不能让你兴奋？
So sex with him isn't exactly waving your flag any more?
这关你屁事，什么笨问题嘛！
That is none of your goddam business! What kind of questions are these?
你惹了很大的麻烦，最好合作点
You're in a lot of trouble, so I suggest you cooperate.
即使问到更私人的问题
If we want to know the most intimate details about your life...
你也要回答
you'd better tell us.
我先生是个好人
My husband is a good man.
但却不能让你心动，对不对？
But he's not exactly ringing your bell these days, is he?
你不介意我来问这段吧？
Let me handle this part. Do you mind?
为什么你去卡洛斯的藏身处？
Why did you go to Carlos' hideout?
他要我假扮成他太太
He wanted me to go to Paris with him on a mission...
和他一起到巴黎去办案
to pose as his wife.
而你居然答应了？
And you agreed?
为什么？
Why?
不知道
I don't know.
我猜我需要一点证明
I guess I needed something.
什么样的证明？
What did you need?
证明我仍活着
I needed to feel alive.
我只想做点惊人之事
I just wanted to do something outrageous.
而且被人需要的感觉…
And it felt really good...
实在很好
to be needed.
还有被人信任
And to be trusted.
和受到特别的待遇
And to be special.
让我怎么说呢？
It's just that there's...
在这一生中，我想做很多事
so much I wanted to do with this life...
却一样也没完成
and it's like I haven't done any of it.
而时间正在慢慢流失中
And the sand's running out of the hourglass...
我希望将来回顾时，能说…
and I wanted to be able to look back and say...
“这些我都做过”
"See? I did that!
“我狂过、我野过”
I was reckless and I was wild and I fucking did it!"
“我他妈的全做过”
Quite frankly, I don't give a shit...
说实话，我根本不在乎你们懂不懂
whether you understand that or not.
这个西蒙…
This Simon...
你和他上过床吗？
did you sleep with him?
没有
No.
她在说谎
She's lying.
你没和他发生性行为？
You did not have sexual relations with him?
你听着，如果每个问题你都问两次
Listen, if you're gonna ask me every question twice...
那要花掉很多时间
this is gonna take a really long time,
而我还得赶着回家
and I have to get back to my family.
女士，你哪里也别想去
You're not going anywhere, lady.
让我离开这里！
Just let me out of here!
回答我的问题
Answer the question.
快回答！
Answer the question!
没有！我…没有…
No! I did not...
和他上床
sleep with him!
请冷静下来
Calm down, please.
听到了吗？卑鄙的杂种！
You hear me, you chickenshit bastard?
不要激动
Calm down.
她说的可能是实话
She could be telling the truth.
达斯克太太，别激动
Calm down, Mrs. Tasker.
请你冷静下来
Calm down, please.
我只剩下一个问题了，达斯克太太
I've only one more question, Mrs. Tasker.
是什么？
What?
你仍旧爱你的丈夫吗？
Do you still love your husband?
是的，我爱他
Yes, I love him.
过去爱他
I've always loved him...
将来也会永远爱他
and I will always love him.
好啦，她爱你，现在怎么办？
She loves you. Now what?
达斯克太太
现在唯一解决的办法是…
There's only one solution to your problem, Mrs. Tasker.
你必须替我们工作
You must work for us.
你在搞什么鬼，哈瑞？
What are you doing?
我想给她个任务
Just giving her a little assignment.
你别开玩笑了！
You gotta be shitting me!
既然她想冒险，那就成全她
She wants a little adventure, so I'm gonna give her one.
我给你一个选择
I'm offering you a choice.
如果替我们工作，那就不起诉
If you work for us, we will drop the charges...
而你能继续过着正常的生活
and you can go back to your normal life.
如果不答应，就去坐牢
If not, you will go to a federal prison...
这样将使你的先生和女儿受到羞辱
and your husband and daughter will be left humiliated and alone.
而且你的一生将被毁掉
Your life will be destroyed.
嗯…让我想想看
Gee. Let me think.
好还是不好？
Yes or no?
当然是好啦
Of course yes.
要我做什么？
What's involved?
我们会用电话和你联络
You will be contacted with the assignment.
联络的密码是波里斯
The code name of your contact will be Boris.
你的密码是…
Your code name will be...
- 娜塔莎？  - 不是
- Natasha? - No.
桃乐丝
Doris.
混球！
You son of a bitch.
卡洛斯，你这混蛋
你以为能躲一辈子吗？
Did you think you could elude us forever, Carlos?
等等，你们抓错人了，我叫西蒙
Wait! You got the wrong guy. My name's Simon.
让我走，你们不必杀我
Just let me go. There's no need to kill me.
因为我没看到你的脸…
I haven't seen your face...
别脱！我没看见
Don't! I didn't see it! I didn't see it!
是你！
It's you!
你仍然喜欢那部车吗？
Hey, you still interested in that 'Vette at all?
卡洛斯，别装蒜了
Hey, Carlos. The game's over.
我们有文件证明你是国际恐怖份子
Your career as an international terrorist is well documented.
- 不是的！  - 是真的！
- No! - Oh, yeah!
我只不过是个卖车的
I sell cars. That's all!
真的不是什么恐怖份子
Come on. I'm not a terrorist.
其实我胆子很小
I'm actually a complete coward.
一看到枪，我就…天呀！
If I ever saw a gun I'd... Oh, God!
求求你们，别杀我
Oh, please, don't! Don't kill me!
我不是间谍
I'm not a spy.
我什么都不是
I'm nothing!
只是个小人物而已
I'm navel lint!
欺骗女人上床
I have to lie to women to get laid.
而且成功的机率很小
And I don't score much.
都是因为小弟弟不够大
I got a little dick. It's pathetic.
喔，天啊！
Oh, God.
间谍会尿裤子吗？
Would a spy pee himself? Huh?
真的不值得杀我
Please, I'm not worth a bullet.
请饶了我吧
Have mercy, sir.
快滚吧
Get the fuck out of here.
滚呀
Just beat it. Go on.
我知道，一转身你们就会杀我
As soon as I turn, you're gonna shoot me!
你们一定会杀我的
You're gonna shoot me!
那部车我可以免费送你
Please! You can have the car for free.
请你放了我，好吗？
What do you say, huh?
滚吧，神经病
Get lost, dipshit.
昨晚是不是很刺激
So last night must've been pretty exciting for you.
我的车爆胎了
My flat tire?
当时真的有点害怕
Actually, it was a little scary...
因为拖车司机弄了很久
because the tow truck driver took such a long time.
我去接
I'll get it.
喂
Hello?
桃乐丝吗？
Doris?
是的
Yes?
什么事？
仔细听着
Listen carefully.
1小时内到马克斯酒店去
In exactly one hour, go to the Hotel Marquis.
向柜台要，给“桃乐丝”的信
Pick up an envelope marked "Doris" at the front desk...
- 还有，打扮得性感点  - 什么？
- and dress sexy. - What?
喂
不，不，转过去
No, no. Turn around.
要温柔点
Do it doucement.
要慢一点
Do it very slowly.
实在太低级了
You've reached a new all-time low.
真不敢相信，你居然去马克斯酒店
I can't believe you're crazy enough to use the suite at the Marquis.
你以为我负担得起吗？
Do you think I can afford a suite like this on my salary?
到底录完了没有？
Is Jean-Claude done yet?
等一下
Hang on.
真恐怖，是谁写的，哈瑞吗？
Who wrote this shit? Harry?
快好了
It's going great.
有没有给桃乐丝的信吗？
Do you have an envelope for Doris?
我是桃乐丝
This is Doris.
你现在的身份是妓女，名叫米雪
Listen, you are a prostitute named Michelle.
在房间里，会有个男人等你
Go to the room. There will be a man there.
他是贩卖军火的疑犯
He is a suspected arms dealer.
等一等
Now, wait a minute.
你不是…要我…那个吧？
You don't expect me to, uh, you know.
放心，他的嗜好很特殊
No. He has particular tastes.
只喜欢看
He likes to watch.
告诉他原来的女孩卡拉生病了
Tell him that his regular girl, Carla, is sick.
如果他喜欢你，会告诉你怎么做
If he likes you, he will tell you what to do.
在你离开之前…
You must plant the bug...
必须把窃听器装在床边的电话上
near the telephone by the bed before you leave.
如果任务没有完成…
If you do not complete your mission...
所有的约定全部取消
the deal is off.
我快完蛋了
I'm gonna go to hell.
有人在吗？
你好
请喝点香槟
Have some champagne.
到这里来
Come in here.
我叫米雪
My name is Michelle.
卡拉认为你会喜欢我
Carla thought you'd like me.
由我来说话
Let me do the talking.
你可以开始脱衣服了
You may start by unzipping your dress.
不，不，转过去
No, no. Turn around.
要温柔点，要慢一点
Do it doucement. Do it very slowly.
很好
Good.
请把衣服慢慢脱下来
Now slip the dress down slowly.
好
Good.
现在把丝袜一只一只的褪下去
Now slide your nylons off one by one.
我没穿丝袜
I'm not wearing any.
那很好
That's good.
现在，为我跳个舞
Now, dance for me.
不是那样
跳得性感点
Dance sexy.
让双手像情人的双手一样
Let your hands be your lover's hands
爱抚着你的肌肤
on your own skin as you move.
请躺到床上，闭上眼睛
Now lie on the bed and close your eyes.
我以为你只喜欢看
I thought you only liked to watch.
请躺到床上，闭上眼睛
Now lie on the bed and close your eyes.
你这只猪！
You pig!
混蛋
Bastard!
海伦，等一等
Wait, wait, wait.
哈瑞？
Yes, it's Harry.
是我，看起来很奇怪，但我能解释
I know it looks bad, but I can explain.
大家都别动
Nobody move!
不准动
Don't move!
海伦，听他们的话
Helen, just don't do anything.
他和此事无关，我是你们要的人
No, he has nothing to do with it! I'm the one you want!
闭嘴
Shut up!
海伦，不要说话，照他们的话去做
Quiet, Helen. Do what they say.
让这个妓女走吧，她根本不重要
Come on, guys, let the hooker go. She's not important.
你们不需要她
You don't need her.
哈瑞，让我来处理这件事
Harry, please, just let me handle this.
闭嘴！
Shut up!
你到那里干什么？
What were you doing there?
告诉你，你也不相信
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
再说话，就杀了你们
Talk again and I'll kill you!
哈瑞
若我说“很高兴见到你”那是骗人
I wish I could say it's nice to see you again.
你认识她？
You know her?
这种口红的颜色，一点也不适合你
You know, this shade's totally wrong for you.
你那朋友是谁？
So who's your little friend?
我叫海伦・达斯克
I'm Helen Tasker.
他是我丈夫，你是谁？
Harry is my husband. And you are?
这么说，你真是达斯克
So now it's Tasker,
而不是伦奎斯特
not Renquist.
她只不过是我在酒吧认识的妓女
She's just some wacko hooker I met down at the bar.
哈瑞，你是怎么搞的？说实话呀
What is the matter with you? Just tell her the truth!
我们已经结婚，还有一个女儿
We are married, and we have a daughter.
我不认识这个疯女人
I don't know what the crazy bitch is on.
最好先放掉她，我们好能办正事
You should cut her loose so we can get down to business.
那我怎么会有这张照片呢？
Where did I get this then, huh?
我到哪弄来的？
Where did I get this?
在起飞前想要点什么？
Something before takeoff?
很痛的，你这个…
That hurt, you b...
看来她说的是实话
She was telling the truth, wasn't she?
她真的什么也不知道
She really doesn't know.
实在有趣
How interesting.
把他们带进来
Bring them.
很宏伟，是不是？
Incredible, aren't they?
我叫它们为四骑师
I call them the Four Horsemen.
它们代表勇士
They're warrior figures...
是属于波斯帝国大流士的
from the Persian Empire of Darius l...
大约是在公元前500年
around 500 BC.
而且是无价之宝
They're absolutely priceless.
真可惜
Pity.
等等！
Wait, wait!
打开它
Open it.
你知道这是什么吗？
Do you know what this is?
我当然知道
I know what this is.
是蒸气式咖啡机
This is an espresso machine.
不对，应该是雪绵制冰机
It's a snow cone maker. That's what it is.
难道是热水炉吗？
Is it a water heater?
你知道为什么会带你来这吗？
Do you know why you've been brought here?
因为我们要他向世界宣布…
So that this man can verify to the world...
红伐党已经拥有了核武器
the Crimson Jihad is now a nuclear power.
天呀！他只不过是个推销员罢了
How can he do that? He's just a salesman, for Christ's sake.
如果我错了，那你的鲜血…
If I'm wrong about him, the last thing you'll see...
将会喷满他的脸
will be your blood spraying across his face.
它是多重独立导向…
It's a Soviet MIRV-6 from
俄式空中核弹火箭
an SS-22 air launch vehicle.
而这种弹头之中还包含了…
The warhead contains
14.5公斤的强化铀和z
14.5 kilograms of enriched uranium and a plutonium trigger.
相当于3万吨的核能量
The nominal yield is 30 kilotons.
释放她，我就合作
该怎么说呢，我是个间谍
What can I say? I'm a spy.
你这个混蛋、骗子、狗娘养的！
You bastard! You lying son of a bitch!
- 甜心  - 对不起，别叫我甜心
- Sorry, honey. - Don't you call me honey!
永远别想再叫我甜心
You don't ever get to call me honey again!
听到了吗？你这只猪！
You understand me, you pig?
我可以证明他们有核弹头的控制器
And I can verify that they have the arming box...
以及引爆核弹头…
and all the equipment necessary...
所需要的其它装备
to detonate all four warheads.
你们杀了我们的妇女和小孩
You have killed our women and our children...
像懦夫一般…
bombed our cities...
从远处轰炸我们的城市
from afar like cowards...
还居然敢说我们是恐怖份子
and you dare to call us terrorists?
如今，被压迫的我们终于有力量…
Now the oppressed have been given a mighty sword...
向敌人反击了
with which to strike back at their enemies.
（电池将用尽）
除非你们美国人…
Unless you, America...
马上将军事力量…
pulls all military forces...
从波斯湾撤出，并且永不再来
out of the Persian Gulf area immediately and forever...
否则每星期红伐党…
the Crimson Jihad will rain fire...
将血洗一个美国主要城市…
on one major U.S. city each week...
直到你们退出为止
until our demands are met.
首先，在这个无人小岛上…
First, we will detonate one weapon...
引爆一枚炸弹
on this uninhabited island...
好证明我们的实力
as a demonstration of our power...
红伐党是支持人道主义的
and Crimson Jihad's willingness to be humanitarian.
但是，如果你们不撤军
However, if these demands are not met...
那我们只好每星期…
Crimson Jihad will rain fire...
血洗一个美国主要城市
on one major American city each week
电池用完了
Battery.
白痴，去换一个呀
Get another one, you moron.
卡车里…好像还有一个
I think I have one in the truck.
- 干什么？  - 快来看
- What? - Look at this.
那不是我的
That's not mine.
很棒的传送器
Nice transmitter.
迈阿密塔台
Miami Tower,
6479号喷射机准备进入跑道
Jet Star 6479 Delta on final.
- 预计12分钟后着陆  - 好
- We'll be on the ground in 12 minutes. - All right.
让毒品稽查员准备好直升机
Tell those D.E.A. boys to have the helos...
12分钟后起飞
hot and ready to fly in 12 minutes.
讯号停在佛罗里达州的启思岛
Signal's definitely stopped moving. It's an island in the Keys.
讯号消失了
We lost the signal.
糟糕
Shit!
各位，这位就是萨米亚
All right, everyone. This is Samir.
谁能猜出他的专长，就得50分
For 50 points, see if you can guess his specialty.
口腔卫生吗？
No hygiene?
不完全对
Not exactly.
哈瑞，这到底在搞什么？
What's going on?
萨米亚只想问哈瑞几个问题
Samir's just gonna ask Harry a few questions.
我们想知道哈瑞是替谁工作？
We're not even sure which agency Harry works for.
而萨米亚是问询这方面的高手
Now, Samir's absolutely first-class.
当然，哈瑞在这方面也很不赖
On the other hand we have Harry,
居然能欺骗他所爱的女人…
who's managed to lie convincingly...
达15年之久
to the woman he loves for 15 years.
所以我对他到底能抵抗多久
So it'll be interesting to see...
很感兴趣
how long he can resist.
这个会有所帮助
This will help.
你应该先用酒精消毒的
You know, you should swab that with alcohol.
否则我可能会被感染
I might get an infection.
等药力开始时，我会回来
I'll return when this has taken effect.
那时候，我们再谈
Then we'll talk.
我衷心盼望
I'm looking forward to it.
你为什么要帮助那些疯子
Now, why are you helping these raving psychotics?
因为他们有雄厚的资金
Because they're very well-funded raving psychotics...
而且给了我不少的钱
and I'm getting a lot of money.
我才不关心他们的理念
What, you think I care about their cause?
当然也不在乎你的死活
Or yours? Not at all.
你的脑袋有问题，女士
You're damaged goods, lady.
你把我们俩的事情告诉她了吗？
Did you tell her about us?
你这疯婆娘，我们之间根本没什么
There is no "us," you psychopathic bitch.
哦，是吗？
Oh, sure.
你现在当然会这么说
You say that now.
谢谢你给我那段快乐的时光
Thanks for everything. It wasn't bad while it lasted.
我们走
Let's go.
你们俩留下来
You two stay here.
我们之间没什么
There was nothing.
我发誓
I swear.
他给你打了什么针？
What did they give you?
一种说实话的麻醉药
Sodium Amytal, or some other truth agent.
它真会让你说实话吗？
It makes you tell the truth?
药力开始了吗？
Is it working?
问一个通常我会说谎的问题
Ask me a question that I normally would lie to.
我们会死吗？
Are we gonna die?
会
Yep.
看来已经开始了
I'd say it's working.
他们会在我们头上开一枪
They're gonna shoot us in the head,
不然就折磨我们到死
or they're gonna torture us to death...
否则就把我们留在这里，让炸弹…
or they're gonna leave us here and let the bomb...
哈瑞！
你做了多久的间谍？
How long have you been a spy?
17年
Seventeen years.
有没有杀过人？
Have you ever killed anyone?
有，但是他们都是坏人
Yeah, but they were all bad.
在开始之前，你有事要告诉我吗？
Is there anything you want to tell me before we start?
有
Yeah.
我很快就要杀死你们
I'm going to kill you pretty soon.
我知道了
I see.
怎么杀呢？
How, exactly?
首先，我把你当做肉墙
First, I'm going to use you as a human shield.
然后用桌上的套管针
Then I'm going to kill this guard over there...
把那边的守卫杀掉
with the Patterson trocar on the table.
最后再把你的脖子扭断
And then I was thinking about breaking your neck.
你认为能成功吗？
And what makes you think you can do all that?
你记得那副手铐吗？
You know my handcuffs?
我撬开了
I picked them.
我们快离开这里
Let's get out of here.
咱们走！
Come on!
哈瑞！
把枪放下
Drop the gun!
甜心，下次记得先低头
Honey, next time, duck.
我们走
Let's go.
我居然嫁给了肌肉男兰博
I married Rambo.
他们在做什么？
What are they doing?
时间已定下
It is done.
在90分钟内，一柱圣火
In 90 minutes, a pillar of holy fire...
将会点燃天空
will light up the skies...
好让全世界的人知道
to show to the world...
我们讲的是实话
that we speak the truth.
我们的意志坚定
We are set on our course.
没人能阻挡我们
No force can stop us now.
我们很冷静，随时准备牺牲等等
We're cool, we're bad-asses, blah, blah, blah, blah.
若是在岛上，那他们为何用卡车？
If we're on an island, why are they using trucks?
那我们一定是在佛州的启思岛上
We must be in the Florida Keys.
跨海大桥将岛和本土连结起来
The overseas highway connects the islands to the mainland.
这里没有国界、也没海关
There's no borders, no customs.
能长驱直入美国
They can go anywhere in the U.S.
根本阻挡不了他们
There's nothing to stop them.
除了我们
Just us.
把枪拿着
Here, take this.
噢，要命
Oh, shit.
开枪
Shoot!
糟糕
Shit!
没子弹了
该死
好的！
我们走
Let's go.
唉！让我向寡妇致哀吧
My condolences to the widow.
我们可能需要人质
We may need the hostage.
可怜的绝望主妇，走吧
Okay, let's go, Suzy Homemaker.
快点
Hurry up!
把她押到车里，我们出发吧
Just get her in the car. Let's get going.
我就知道，这是你的功劳
I thought this looked like your work.
快走，在飞机上做简报
Let's go. I'll brief you in the air.
别客气，我们走吧！快走
You're welcome. Let's go! Let's get out of here!
我们快走
Let's go! Come on!
请你告诉那个笨蛋，这是紧急情况
Well, you tell that son of a bitch this is a Bright Boy Alert.
重复：紧急情况
I repeat: A Bright Boy Alert.
现在不是演习，你懂吗？
This is not a drill. Do you understand that?
等一下，请替我接白宫
Hold on. Put me through to the White House.
将所有人撤出12哩外
The minimum safe distance is 12 miles.
马上叫海军陆战队…
Get the marine patrol in right away.
海岸警卫队、警察部队去帮忙
I want the Coast Guard and the sheriff's department too.
任何无法撤出的人，就用飞机运送
Anyone that cannot make that distance, you gotta get 'em out by air.
好了，你们只有34分钟
You've got exactly 34 minutes.
有两架侵略者号战斗机…
I can get you two Marine Corps Harriers here...
将在11分钟内抵达
in 11 minutes.
他们现在在启思岛的西方
They're on manoeuvres outside Key West.
让他们来，我会做简报
Get them. I'll brief them on the way in.
请他们马上来
Send 'em in right away.
要来一杯吗？
Would you like one?
要州警用麦克风…
I want the state police driving through the streets...
在街头通知所有居民
on their damn loudspeakers.
他们来了
Here they come.
这是莱姆01号
Lime-Zero-One,
在桥的东方看到三辆卡车
got a tally on three trucks east bound on the bridge.
知道了，莱姆01号，他们是你的了
Roger, Lime-Zero-One. You're clear to engage.
导弹会绕圈子，先用机关枪攻击
Ringo is padlocked. In hot with guns.
我们开始进攻
Let's get some.
陆战队员们，去踢他们的屁股吧
Okay, marines, time to kick ass.
我建议，用精确致导导弹把桥炸断
Recommend using your Mavericks to take out the bridge.
知道了
Roger that.
莱姆战机启动两枚精确致导导弹
Lime flight, switch Mavericks. Two.
它们不会引爆核弹头吧？
These missiles won't set off those nukes, will they?
不会的，莱姆01号
That's a negative.
发射
Fire.
- 宾果  - 射得好，海军陆战队
- Bingo! - Good shooting, marines.
我要杀了你
I'll kill you!
- 车失控了  - 好像有人杀了司机
- It's out of control. - Somebody capped the driver.
泼妇
Bitch!
一瓶够吗？干脆来两瓶
Like one? How about two?
低飞，向轿车接近
Get down to the limo!
低飞，快！
Come on! Take it down! Let's go!
再低点
Get down!
还要低
Take it down.
哈瑞，是你吗？
哈瑞！
桥断了
The bridge is out!
什么？
What?
桥断了
The bridge is out!
我听不到
I can't hear you!
你说什么？
What?
喔，天呀！桥断了
Oh, God! The bridge is out!
哈瑞，桥断了
快，快点呀！
Come on! Come on!
加点速，在这里低飞
Speed up a little bit, now. Get down there.
哈瑞，快点嘛！
Come on! Hurry!
快，拜托快一点
Hurry, Harry!
- 抓住我的手  - 你回来呀！
- Grab my hand! - Come back!
向右一点
Okay, to the right.
我够不着，再低一点
I can't reach! Get lower!
好了，抓紧
Here we go! Hold on!
抓紧点
Hold on really tight!
哈瑞！
Harry!
你快回来！
Come back!
向上一点
Pull up!
抓住我的手
Grab my hand!
- 试试看  - 我够不着
- You can do it!\n- I can't reach!
天呀，哈瑞，快想办法！
Oh, God! Please! Harry!
完了
Oh, shit.
加油，宝贝
Come on, baby.
抓紧
Hold on!
别担心，我抓住你了
I got you!
哇，我的天！
Oh, God!
抓紧点
Hold on tight!
哈瑞！
（公路中间严禁停车）
我们快降落
Let's get this thing on the ground.
所有的飞机快着陆
Let's get these aircraft on the ground.
核弹大约1分钟后就会爆炸
We got a nuclear bomb going off in about one minute.
任何时间都会爆炸
Any minute now. Go, go, go.
快给我扩音器
Come here. Give me a bullhorn.
好了，现在是“表演”时间
All right, it's show time.
不要注视闪光
Do not look at the flash. Do not look at the flash!
这里应该很安全
We should be safe here.
你怎么能戴错手指呢？
This is the wrong finger.
哈瑞
哈瑞，来这里一下
Come here!
- 去办事吧  - 好，拜拜
- Go to work. - Okay. Bye.
阿兹的直升机20分钟前…
Aziz's copter landed about 20 minutes ago
降落在迈阿密大厦上
on top of a high-rise in Miami.
他和他的党员聚集在20楼
He rendezvoused with some faction members. They're on the 20th floor.
反恐特警已到达，警察封锁了现场
I got SWAT down there. The cops cordoned off the area.
他们所握有的人质，是达娜
They got a hostage. It's Dana.
你什么意思？我女儿达娜？
What do you mean? My Dana?
是的，哈瑞
真抱歉我不知该说什么
I'm real sorry. I don't know what to say.
我猜他是在半夜把她抓走
I guess he grabbed her in the middle of the night.
我们刚刚才知道
We just found out about it.
你别担心，我们会把她安全带回来
But I don't want you to worry. We'll get her back.
因为我有内线在里面
I've got a guy on the inside. Listen.
一定会把她带回来
We're gonna get her back.
他又自做主张了
Here we go.
队长，打扰，我得借一下飞机
Excuse me, Captain. I got to borrow your plane for a minute.
指挥官下令要你们默契配合，对吧？
Listen, Force Comm cleared you to give us total cooperation, right?
所谓的指挥官就是美国总统
And you know that comes directly from the president of these United States.
但你必须要先签字
But, sir, you're gonna have to sign for this aircraft.
我会签的，有笔吗？
I'll sign for it. You got a pen? You take care of it.
你去准备文件，好吗？
Do you realize it has been ten years...
你已经10年没飞过这种飞机了
since you've been behind the wheel of one of these?
弄坏的话，就扣我薪水
I break it, they can take it out of my pay.
哈瑞，你听着，我们有内线
Listen, we got a guy on the inside.
大家快向后退，快走
Gotta move back, everybody! Let's go!
你在做什么？
你们别担心，不会有问题的
All right, everybody, it's gonna be all right!
他有100小时的飞行训练
He's got hundreds of hours in the Harriers there.
虽然有点生疏
He is a little rusty,
但那是他一贯的起飞方式
but that's a trademark Tasker takeoff.
就像骑脚踏车，永远不会忘记
It's like riding a bike. You never forget, really.
我们最好先躲一下
We might wanna seek shelter!
抱歉
Sorry.
太差劲了吧？
Fuck!
街上围满了观望者
The streets are filled with people...
警方正在疏散大厦中的人
as police try to evacuate the buildings.
恐怖组织正朝天疯狂射击
They appear to be shooting wildly into the air as I'm speaking.
似乎是预警
These seem to be warning shots.
但到目前为止
So far...
没向我们或警方开枪
they have not fired at us or police.
很明显的…
This apparently is...
他们和引爆启思岛的…
the same group which just detonated a nuclear bomb...
暴徒是同一组织
in the Florida Keys.
红伐党每个星期…
Crimson Jihad will...
将血洗一个美国主要城市
rain fire on one major U.S. city each week...
直到你们退出为止
until our demands are met.
这个录影带是在恐怖份子…
This tape was released to the media just minutes after the terrorists
我要上厕所
I have to go to the bathroom.
现场实况报导后
We'll repeat the tape...
我们会重播这段录影带
following this live report from the scene.
不要开枪
Hold your fire!
你要求的录影小组到了
The video crew you wanted is here!
让他们进来
Send them!
他们进来了，没有携带武器
They're coming in. They're unarmed.
好，去吧
Come on. Let's go.
快点
Go.
这是红伐党的公告
This is a communiqu? from Crimson Jihad.
你们已经看到我们的力量
You have seen a demonstration of our power.
别逼我毁掉这个城市
Do not force us to destroy this city...
也不要与我们对抗
and do not try to use force against us.
我们视死如归
I, we are all prepared to die.
只要把那个钥匙一转
With one turn of that key...
200万的市民就会立即死亡
two million of your people will die instantly!
- 什么钥匙？  - 就是那个钥匙
- What key? - That key!
谁拿走了？
Who's taken the key?
射她！
Shoot her!
好险呀！
Holy shit!
第一组呼叫第七组，情况怎样？
Unit One to Unit Seven. Give me a situation report.
第七组，报告现况
One to Seven. Give me a sit rep.
费絮，听到吗？
Faisil, do you copy?
这是第七组，已攻下第21楼
Seven here. 21st floor secure.
在20楼内大约有12个党徒
About 12 faction members on the 20th floor.
没有人质
No hostages there.
- 达娜呢？  - 她在屋顶上
- Where's Dana? - She's on the roof.
好，你们等我，再把地址讲一遍
Okay, stay put. Give me that address again.
你杀了我，钥匙就会掉下去
You shoot me, this'll fall!
你待在那里，别过来！
Stay where you are! Stay where you are!
把钥匙给我
Give me the key!
我发誓会把它丢下去！
I'll drop it, I swear!
不要
把钥匙给我
Give me the key.
孩子，你并不想死，对吗？
Come on, child. You don't want to die, do you?
把钥匙给我，我就不伤你
Give me the key and you won't get hurt.
我向你保证
I give you my word!
别做梦了，你这个疯子
No way, you wacko!
救命！
Help me!
不要再过来
Please don't come any closer!
救命呀！
Help me!
谁来帮我呀！
Somebody!
快来救我！
Help me!
达娜，跳下来
Dana, jump down!
快跳下来！
Jump down!
爸？
Dad?
救我呀！
Help me!
爸！
Daddy!
爸，快回来！
Daddy, come back!
爸，救我下来！
Daddy, get me down!
爸！
Daddy!
跳下来
Jump! Jump!
我会接住你的
Daddy will catch you!
- 跳呀！  - 我不敢跳
-Jump! - I can't!
抓紧
Hold on!
爸，千万别让我掉下去！
Don't you let me fall, please!
- 爸！  - 别害怕
- Daddy! - I got you!
我要滑下去了
I'm slipping!
不！达娜
救我，我要滑下去了！
Help me! I'm gonna fall!
抓住我的手
Hold my hand!
抓紧点
Hold on tight, honey.
他在你后面！
He's behind you!
快降落，否则就杀了她！
Take this plane down, now! I'll kill her!
快降落，就现在！
Take it down, now!
天啊，想点办法呀！
My God, do something!
（发射钮）
你被炒了
You're fired.
好啦，没事了
It's okay.
达娜
甜心，都结束了
Honey, it's over.
嗨，小鬼头
Hi, pumpkin.
飞机刚一降落…
Just seconds after the jet landed...
身份不明的驾驶员…
the unidentified pilot was escorted...
马上由FBI护送离去
from the scene by Federal agents.
虽然我们不清楚…
Though it is unclear at this moment...
今早是哪个单位的探员
which agency was responsible...
这么戏剧化的结束了…
for the operation which ended the terrorist threat...
一场恐怖组织的威胁
so dramatically early this morning...
但据迈阿密警方的消息…
we've learned from Miami Police Do it properly.
（一年后）
一、二、三、四，开始拇指战
One, two, three, four, I declare a thumb war.
五、六、七、八，竖起拇指来
Five, six, seven, eight, try to keep your thumbs straight.
不要这样！停止
Don't! Stop it!
等一下
Wait!
我逮到你了
I got you!
你要听清楚规则
Just listen. Listen to the rules.
喂
Hello?
是波里斯和桃乐丝吗？
Boris and Doris?
我们有任务了
We're on.
是的，请说
Yes? Go ahead.
上校，真高兴又见到你
Colonel, how nice to see you again.
晚上好
Good evening.
她是谁？
Who was that?
情况如何？看到接头人了吗？
What's the scoop, team? You see your contact yet?
还没看到
Haven't seen him yet.
但是有个人，我倒想打个招呼
But I see somebody I'd like to say hello to.
再替你添点香槟
Let me pour you some more champagne.
我一定要扮得像个服务生
I got to keep up the waiter bit.
一般来说，监视有时很危险
These stakeouts can be tricky.
随时都会有生死攸关的情况发生
You never know when things might explode into a life-or-death situation.
如果真的发生你先躲起来
If it gets rough, stay low until it's over...
以后会联络你
and I'll contact you later.
最好把你的…
Maybe you should give me your...
嗨，卡洛斯，又见面了
So, we meet again, Carlos.
甜心，我就在这里解决他吧？
Honey, I'm just gonna do him right here, okay?
好呀
Go for it.
喔，天呀
Oh, God.
你不是没有害怕的权利吗？
Fear is not an option.
跳舞吧
Dance?
哦，不要啊
探戈
- Tango. - Here we go.
哈瑞、海伦，伙计们，拜托别跳了
Harry? Helen? Guys? Come on, now.
否则会分散注意力的
Let's not get distracted.
我们还有重要的事要办
We got some work to do.
好啦，别这样嘛
All right, guys. Come on.
你们最好正经点
You guys better get serious in there.
换成我就会很认真
I'd be serious if I was in there.
哈瑞，别不理我，那样很不礼貌
Don't ignore me, Harry. That's rude.
好啦，伙计们，别酱子
All right, guys. Come on.
这牵涉到国家安全
National security, guys.
是生死攸关的大事
Come on. Life and death.
制片主任：斯科特・特勒\n帕特立夏・威彻尔
哈瑞？
助理导演：J. 迈克尔・海尼\n艾迪克・拉奥利・波特\n马丁・杰德利卡
海伦，我一直是站在你那边的
Helen, I was always on your side.
制片：帕米拉・伊斯利
而且每次都帮你
I was always there for you.
特技师：托马斯・费舍尔
音效：伟烈・斯德特曼\n格雷格・贝克斯特\n民克・民科尔\n罗伯特・毕默
告诉你们，我不想再待在车里了
You know what? I'm sick of being in the van.
下次换你们呆着
You guys are gonna be in the van next time.
真不公平
为何15年来都是我待在车里？
I been in the van for 15 years.